solveigmm.com 2019-12-22

# Privacy Policy

The Privacy Policy will address the following points:

What information, if any, is collected as a result of your visit?  
Whether information is shared?  
Whether Cookies are placed on your hard drive?  
Contact Information

**Introduction**  
Protecting personal information is a core Solveig Multimedia value. This privacy statement describes how we collect and use the personal information you provide on our website. It also describes the choices available to you regarding the use of your personal information and the steps you can take to access this information and to request that we correct or delete it.

Solveig Multimedia abides by the safe harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of data from the European Union.

**Information Collection**  
As is true of most websites, we gather information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and click-stream data. We use this information, which does not identify individual visitors, to analyze trends, to administer the website, to track visitors' movements around the site and to gather information about the geographic location of our visitors as a whole. We do not collect Personally Identifiable Information ("PII") about our visitors at this website. No further information regarding our visitors, other than the browser-level information described above, is collected at this website in any manner whatsoever or for any purpose.

**Cookies**  
A "cookie" is a small file containing a string of characters that is sent to your computer when you visit a website. When you visit the website again, the cookie allows that site to recognize your browser. Cookies may store user preferences and other information. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some website features or services may not function properly without cookies.

We use cookies to enhance your online experience and to learn about how you use our services in order to improve the quality of our services. Specific cookies usage include:

  * Storing your Preferences and Settings. Settings that enable the Site to operate correctly or that maintain your preferences over time may be stored on your device.
  * Social Media. The Site include social media cookies, including those that enable users who are logged in to the social media service to share content via that service.
  * Analytics. In order to provide analyze the performance of the Site, we use cookies to gather usage and performance data. Our servers automatically record information when you visit our website, including the URL, IP address, browser type and language, and the date and time of your request. This may include cookies from third-party analytics providers.

Most web browsers automatically accept cookies but provide controls that allow you to block or delete them. Instructions for blocking or deleting cookies in browsers may be available in each browser's privacy or help documentation. If you use different devices or browsers you should apply such settings to all of them accordingly.

**Sharing of Information**  
As described above, no information other than the browser-level information, and the information recorded by the cookie (IP address, browser type and language, and the date and time of your request for information) is captured by visiting our website. The browser-level information and information recorded by the cookie is not shared with any third party.

**Policy Changes**  
We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes in a conspicuous manner to this Privacy Policy, and other places we deem appropriate, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

**Contact Information**  
If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact us at:

Solveig Multimedia  
3 Razvitiya prospekt  
Tomsk, 634055, Russian Federation  
E-mail: [info@solveigmm.com](mailto:info@solveigmm.com)

© Solveig Multimedia

All trademarks are the property of their respective owners. All Rights Reserved.
